<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Parker SC47]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Parker SC47]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 19:42:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I bought my first airplane on December 7, 1991 in State College, PA. A Bellanca Cruisair, 14-13-2 - N86728, Ser# 1089. I hangared the plane at the Greeville Downtown Airport (KGMU). One of our first trips in the plane was to Hartsville, SC to visit Jane’s mother. Shortly after taking off from GMU, heading to the the SE and still climbing - we passed over what looked to me like a grass strip about 10 miles from GMU, I made a mental note. A few months later, same trip to Hartsville and again I saw the same grass strip. In 1994 I inquired at the Williamsport private airpark on the NE side of Easley about lots that were for sale there, at that time it was still. I began to consider buying one. Another thought was to find some land and start an airpark. The ‘airstrip’ I saw on our trips to Hartsville was worth looking into, just go out and find it and look for the owner. I flew out to the area i remembered seeing it, flew around in circles, searched for it more than once and could not find it. Went back to GMU, landed, took off agin and started out on a flight to Hartsville - a few minuts later there it was. I had an early handheld GPS unit, captured its location, flew around the area and sketched the roads from there back to Simpsonville and landed back at GMU. Drove to Simpsonville and follwed the landmarks and roads I diagrammed, went straight to the ‘airfield’. I found a metal farm gate along Stewart Road just past the old peach packing shed, parked there and walked along the tractor path to the ‘runway’. It was grown up completely to over waist hieght but it looked like a runway, long and wide. Walked back to my truck and found another truck with two men standing there. Introduced myself to Harold Cooper and his companion. The runway and surrounding 107 acres belonged to Harold. He told me that another person a decade earlier had bought the land from him, carved in a runway and tried to develop and airpark. I did some research and found that _FILL IN_ had proposed at least three plans for the development and sale of a residential airpark surrounding the runway - one of about 45 lots, one of around 24 lots, and one of 8 lots. After trying for a few years to make it happen, he stopped making mortgage payments to Harold and paying county taxes; Harold had to go after the arrears payments and pay the county back taxes to get the land back. I had initial discussions with Harold about my plans and his desire to sell the property. After the first discussions I continued to scout around, the southern Greenville County area and into adjoining counties for any other suitable airpark tracts - I found nothing as good. At one of the early meetings with Harold he told me that he would not take less than $5000 per acre for the 107 acres. When I came back to Harold after about three months of pulling a proposal together he said the price per acre was $7500. I reminded him that he had told me earlier that the price was $5000; he reminded me that he didn’t say that the price was $5000 - he said that he wouldn’t take less than $5000, that was different. We agreed to move forward with $7500 per acre and I would start with my planning. After getting onto its history I found a few reasons why the plans for an airpark did not pan out for __. First, he was over extended into this and other development projects elsewhere. Second, the economy was in a mild recession, buyers were scarce. Third, and likely the biggest problem was that during the grading of the runway, the weather was very dry and dust silt went airborne and floated into an adjoining neighbor’s swimming pool just off of the NE end of the runway, I heard that it was in large quantities. And, there was a dispute with that land owner over a sliver of property common to both tracts, maybe around a half an acre worth. Both of these issues became legal bouts, which may have turned off potential buyers discouraging them from buying any lots.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedi-bought-my-first-airplane-on-december-7-1991-in-state-coll/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">77ffb5ce-3c84-464c-8f2f-54131b877709</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 19:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>